freegamesjungle.com 2018-12-24

# Free games Jungle - Privacy Policy

|  |   
---  
  
### Personal Information  
  
Free Games Jundle (FGJ) always was and always will be a safe gaming experience online. Freegamesjungle.com is committed to protecting your online privacy. freegamesjungle.com does **not** collect any personal information on its servers. Any details that could track you behaviour, visited pages, or locations are NOT stored on our servers. Users of the free online game portal (Free Games Jungle) must repect our terms of service (read more).   
  
---  
  
### Your privacy 100% safe  
  
At Free Games Jungle we do not believe in business cases and traffic tracking. Our codes do not create or read from cookies and our server has log files disabled. We have no idea how many users are on the website and what our users are doing. And why would we? FGJ (Free Games Jungle) was created to bring the best free online games to gamers selected by gamers. Now you know that freegamesjungle.com is a safe place to play the best daily free online games! There are third parties advertising on this portal. Keep reading this privacy statement to learn more about our third parties.   
  
---  
  
### No Ip address Logging  
  
Your IP address is -not- used to gather broad demographic information and we do -not- track your general visiting paterns (how many pages you view while at one website, downloads, etc). We believe in (and focus on) bringing you the best possible free gaming experience. Our sole intention is to bring you the best free online games possible.   
  
---  
  
### Third Party Advertisements  
  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit freegamesjungle.com. These companies may execute scripts and cookies, and use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.   
  
---  
  
### Sharing Of Information  
  
There are no scripts or programs running on our server that store your information. We allow our third party advertisers to host scripts on our webpages. Third party advertisers might collect, store and use your information. These scripts are not property of our game portal website and are subject to the privacy policy of the third party. Find the links to the third party privacy policies in the sections below to learn more.   
  
---  
  
### Third Party Cookies  
  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

Please read the opt-out section how you can protect your privacy be preventing advertisement cookies on your machine.

Find the full policy of our third party advertisers here:

Freegamesjungle has no control on the scripts and server configuration of third parties. Our third parties serve and execute scripts from their remote server. The privacy policy of any third party may change in the future.   
  
---  
  
### What are cookies?  
  
Cookies are digital text files that can be created by any remote connection that you make in your browser. A cookie can only store text or (binairy) numbers or a combinations of both. Because cookies are just text files, created and controlled by your browser, it's a harmless system for your computer health. However you need to be aware that websites, mobile apps and advertisers are able to write and read certain 'invisible' information on the background while you think you are just browsing some online or mobile App content. Our website is NOT using performance cookies and is NOT tracking your behaviour. However we are using third-party advertisers that might use cookies - please read the [third party] section of our privacy policy for more information about our third parties.   
  
---  
  
### Opt Out  
  
Its possible to prevent third party cookies being set on your machine by using the opt-out service [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

**Note:** the optout service itself is creating cooking on your machine as well (caution!) Freegamesjungle.com is not the operator of the opt-out service, we advice all our users to read the networkadvertising.org TOS to be fully aware of their terms.   
  
---  
  
### Liability  
  
It is freegamesjungle.com's policy to respond quickly to claims of intellectual property violation. Upon receiving notification in accordance with any related copyright organization or owner, freegamesjungle.com will immediately disable and remove games in question. Find more information about our copyright policy here
